equinoxfitness.com 2015-12-18

# Privacy Policy

## DIGITAL PRIVACY POLICY

This Digital Privacy Policy ( **“Privacy Policy”** ) describes the privacy practices of Equinox Holdings, Inc. and its subsidiaries operating under the EQUINOX brand ( **“Equinox”** ) in connection with the Equinox websites and the applications designed for download and use by Equinox members on mobile devices (collectively, **“Digital Properties”** ) By using the Digital Properties, and the features and services made available through the Digital Properties, you are acknowledging that you have read, understand and agreed to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and expressly consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information, as described in this Privacy Policy. 

We use the personal information collected through the Digital Properties in an effort to fulfill our commitment to offering and providing unparalleled member service. This Privacy Policy is intended to describe the personal information that is collected from users of the Digital Properties and how it is used and disclosed by or on behalf of Equinox. 

This Privacy Policy may change as we continue to evolve our business, as well as the Digital Properties and the features and services made available through the Digital Properties. If we change this Privacy Policy, we will post the revised document here, and such changes will be effective immediately upon that posting. Your continued use of the Digital Properties constitutes your acceptance of such changes and agreement to be bound by the modified Privacy Policy, and so we recommend that you review this Privacy Policy periodically when accessing or using the Digital Properties. 

This Privacy Policy was last updated on: April 6, 2015 

#### WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT:

When users access and use the Digital Properties, we may collect information that identifies or relates to the user, which includes, without limitation: 

**Contact and Demographic Information:** Information on how to contact users, such as their name, e-mail address, phone number, mailing address and zip code, which they may provide to us when, for example, they inquire about our company, membership, their account, or when they subscribe to receive one of our mailing lists.  This may also include certain demographic information such as date of birth, age and gender.

**Registration and Membership Information:** Information provided when users establish an account on the Digital Properties, such as their email address, username, password, and other contact information provided, as well as information they provide in connection with their Digital Properties account, such as a profile picture.  If a user is an Equinox member, we may also collect their membership number and information, as well as information about how they use and interact with Equinox clubs and the Digital Properties, such as when they use our Digital Properties to check-in to an Equinox club, log a workout, schedule personal training or spa appointments or add a class your schedule.  If users have established a Digital Properties account, they may log in to it in order to review and update their information and preferences.

**Transaction Information:** Information related to a user’s purchase of goods and services through the Digital Properties, such as their credit/debit card information, billing address, the goods and services they purchased, and other related transaction information.

**Usage Information:** Information about a user’s Internet connection, browser, or computer/device, IP address or device ID, and information on how they use and interact with the Digital Properties, such as pages or features they access. 

**Social Media and Third Party Apps:** If a user links their social media profiles and accounts to the Digital Properties, or otherwise interacts with the Digital Properties through social media networks (e.g., by clicking a Facebook “like” button), information may made available to, and collected by, the Digital Properties through those social media profiles and accounts.  In addition, if a user elects to connect their third party fitness devices or third party applications (collectively “ **Third Party Apps** ”) to the Digital Properties in order to utilize certain features and functionalities, we may collect information from such Third Party Apps.

#### 

**HOW WE USE PERSONAL INFORMATION:**

We use the personal information collected through our Digital Properties to provide users with the services and products they request, to deliver a more relevant and curated experience with the Digital Properties and relationship with Equinox, and to satisfy our other business purposes and needs. This may include, without limitation, using that information in connection with:

**Transaction Fulfillment:** Providing users with the goods, services or information they have requested, and to respond to inquiries, requests and comments from users.

**Promotional Materials:** Communicating special offers, promotions and information about our company and service offerings to users via email or to their mailing address, if they have provided one.  We may also send users newsletters and information about products, services and promotions of our business partners and affiliates.  If users do not wish to receive these promotional emails, they can opt out of future promotional mailings by clicking on the unsubscribe link located on the bottom of the relevant promotional email.  If users maintain an account on our Digital Properties, they can also unsubscribe to promotional mailings at any time by adjusting their communications preferences within their account.  Although we strive to update our email list as frequently as possible, users might receive another contact before we are able to remove them from our lists.  Please note that even if users opt-out of receiving promotional emails, they will continue to receive Member Services related communications as it pertains to their member account, as described below. 

**Membership Communications:** Providing members with administrative communications, announcements and information about their membership such as information regarding club hours or billing reminders.  Equinox may use any contact information held on file (including email, mailing address, telephone or mobile phone and fax) to communicate with a member in relation to day-to-day administrative activities, such as freeze requests, online purchases and important service alerts.

**Personalized Experience:** Delivering a more relevant and curated experience to members, including by recommending services or content we think members will enjoy.  As part of our efforts to provide members with a more personalized experience, we may combine the information regarding a member and collected through the Digital Properties with other information that we have collected from a member in the course of his or her relationship with Equinox, including, without limitation, information collected offline when the member checks in to and use our facilities, information the member volunteers when completing assessments and questionnaires regarding physical health, nutrition and fitness goals, and information about the member, such as training logs, provided by personal trainers and other Equinox staff.

**Business Purposes and Research:** Analyzing and improving the services we offer (including on or through the Digital Properties), better understanding our business and members, evaluating products and services that may be of interest to users, and carrying out internal purposes and research and otherwise operating our business.  This may include aggregating  information regarding users across our entire user base or part of our user base.

#### 

HOW WE SHARE INFORMATION:

Except as described in this Privacy Policy or in other situations where we have otherwise provided clear prior notice to users, Equinox does not sell, rent or otherwise share the name, e-mail address, or any other personally identifiable information of users to unaffiliated third parties.  We may, however, share information for the following reasons and with the following persons: 

**Agents and Service Providers:** We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf.  Examples include creating and maintaining our Web site, sending postal mail and e-mail, managing and updating customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance and providing customer service. They have access to users’ personal information in order to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. 

**Social Media and Third Party Apps:** We may share information with social networks when users interact with the Digital Properties (e.g., a clicking a Facebook “like” button) or connect their social media accounts to the Digital Properties.  If a user elects to connect Third Party Apps to the Digital Properties, their information may also be shared with these third parties.  Please see below for more information on this, as we do not control these third parties or their privacy practices.

**Compliance and Protection:** We reserve the right to disclose any personal information we have concerning users if we determine doing so is necessary or desirable to: comply with our obligations under the law or in connection with any legal process or investigative or governmental requests; enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Equinox, its affiliates, our users, members or employees, or others.  This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection, as well as providing information to law enforcement and governmental authorities.

**Corporate Transactions:** In the event of a reorganization, merger or sale of Equinox or any of its affiliates, we may transfer any and all personal information we have collected to the relevant third party.

**Aggregated Information:** We may also share aggregated statistical data with partners that includes users' demographic information but does not identify them.  We reserve the right to provide any and all such aggregated and de-identified data to third parties. 

#### USE OF COOKIES:

We use cookies and similar technologies such as web beacons to enhance your experience on our web site. For example a cookie enables us to remember the region or specific club page you have visited so the next time you return to our site you do not have to select that club or region again.

You can adjust how your Internet browser (like Chrome or Safari) responds to cookies (e.g., to warn you every time a cookie is sent, or to turn off all cookies). See your browser's Help menu for these instructions. By disabling your cookies, please understand you will not have access to some of the features that enhance your user experience on the Digital Properties.

Equinox does not currently allow third parties to collect personally identifiable information about an individual user’s online activities over time and across different websites when that individual uses the Digital Properties and therefore does not respond to web browser “do not track” signals.

#### 

**USE BY ADULTS AND TEENAGERS:**

Equinox offers membership to individuals who are at least 18 years of age. However, teenagers that are at least 16 years of age may also join with the written consent of a parent.  Similarly, the Digital Properties are intended for use by adults, and when we collect information through the Digital Properties for membership inquiry purposes, users are informed they must be at least 18 years of age or, for teenagers ages 16 to 18, have parental consent to provide personally identifying information to us. The Digital Properties are not intended for children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect or store any personal information from children under the age of 13.  

#### 

**THIRD PARTY SITES AND APPS:**

While the Digital Properties may contain links to other sites, products or services, please note that when you click on one of these links, you are 'clicking' away from the Digital Properties and accessing a third party’s website, app or other digital property.  In addition, certain features of the Digital Properties may enable you to connect the Digital Properties to, or otherwise share your information with, Third Party Apps. 

Please understand that these third parties may collect information about users which will be used under their privacy policies.  We encourage users to read the privacy polices of these third parties, as their practices may differ from ours. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE PRIVACY PRACTICES OR THE COLLECTION OR USE OF A USER’S INFORMATION FROM ANY SUCH THIRD PARTIES.

#### HOW TO CONTACT EQUINOX:

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Policy, other areas of our Web site or our clubs, please [contact us](http://www.equinox.com/contactus) by visiting [http://www.equinox.com/contactus](http://www.equinox.com/contactus). Your feedback is always welcome and appreciated.
